<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VamX-Virtual Audio Manipulation Experience on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/master/m6-vamx/</link>
    <description>Recent content in VamX-Virtual Audio Manipulation Experience on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/master/m6-vamx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/master/m6-vamx/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/master/m6-vamx/features/</guid>
      <description>Features To monitor heart rate, which is a measure of stress, we have integrated a Bluetooth interface into the framework. A paired heart rate device passes on its measured data to VamX. The course of the heart rate is displayed as a graph in the framework in real time.
VamX and heart rate measuring instrument are connected via bluetooth. For testing the framework we have developed three VR games. Based on their different characteristics, various predictions and scenarios are to be drawn for one&amp;rsquo;s own application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/master/m6-vamx/techstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/master/m6-vamx/techstack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack Unity Within the Unity game engine, we developed the sound framework and built the VR test environment. It provided us with many build-in features for programming with sounds and was well suited for development with VR. XR Interaction Toolkit The XR Interaction Toolkit offered us all the basic functions for interaction in VR. With the help of input events and haptic feedback, we were able to make the minigames more interesting and created a good gaming experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/master/m6-vamx/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/master/m6-vamx/process/</guid>
      <description> Download You can download VamX and the games here. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
