<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Missing Tool on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The Missing Tool on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Finding Ideas</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/finding-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/finding-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Creative minds trying to find a clear vision In the beginning of our project, we didn&amp;rsquo;t have a clear product vision yet. We had many ideas in mind, from designing little telepresence games like &amp;ldquo;Who Am I?&amp;rdquo;, a flexible poll tool up to an online-tutoring platform for students.
Our brainstorming process As interesting as all of those ideas would have been, the spark has not yet jumped. We had to do another round and really ask ourselves – and our supervisor Barne – what it really is that we want to achieve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Vision</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/product-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/product-vision/</guid>
      <description>Group projects in no time ... After several weeks of defining and shaping our ideas, we came up with our final vision: A tool that makes it possible for students to brainstorm ideas on notes that can be used on a digital whiteboard, to communicate in real-time about the delevoped ideas and to easily form new sub-groups without the trouble of joining new breakout-rooms. ... and with no effort at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/features/</guid>
      <description>Show me your cards! The main features of our tool include creating boards with notes on which you can collect ideas, communicate with each other and find new working groups. We tried to make our tool as user-friendly as possible and reduced unnecessary things so the thought process does not get interrupted. This is why The Missing Tool is so lightweight – you don&amp;rsquo;t even need to create a user account!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Focus</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/our-focus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/our-focus/</guid>
      <description>Whatever you need, whenever you need it We made a huge progress in defining our final product vision when we asked ourselves what the specific use cases for our product were. We wanted to provide a tool that gives you the freedom to do what you need to do at the specific moment to make your group-project work, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t overwhelm you with fancy features that you most likely won&amp;rsquo;t make any use of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Node.js &amp;amp; Socket.io We made use of Node.js, which is an asynchronous event-driven JavaScript runtime and designed to build scalable network applications. Together with Socket.io, which enables real-time, bidirectional and event-based communication, we had the perfect base for building our application. MongoDB We decided to work with MongoDb, which is a document-oriented database system, classified as a NoSQL database program. It is really simple to use, but offers deep query-abilities at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/future-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss20/bachelor/b5-the-missing-tool-projekt/future-features/</guid>
      <description>So, what&amp;#39;s next? If we have had more time, we probably would have come up with so much more ideas of what to integrate in The Missing Tool. And we already had some ideas that we would like to be realized in the future – either by us or some other students who will get a chance to work on the tool. Audiochat We want to give our users the opportunity to chat via audio, as an addition to the chat that is already present.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
