<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bloompipe on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b1-bloompipe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bloompipe on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b1-bloompipe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b1-bloompipe/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b1-bloompipe/features/</guid>
      <description>WebApp Our WebApp is part of our website which guides you through the process of creating your own music video. Within there, you are enabled to select different video generation styles and AI presets of varying degrees of complexity. Whether you are a casual music fan or a proficient digital artist - Bloompipe will suit your needs.
Styles To have the style of the video match your taste, we are providing different options, with which the music videos can be generated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b1-bloompipe/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b1-bloompipe/process/</guid>
      <description>The Process Our journey began with our aspiration to create an art creating tool. Based on this idea, we planned out some milestones to achieve this goal. This, of course, should help us over time to plan and structure our project as well as possible. For this task we used agile methods which helped us to complete the project. We held our weekly meetings every Monday and on Tuesday mornings with our professor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b1-bloompipe/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b1-bloompipe/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Organisation and Communication For organizing our internal teams and for everything else we used the following platforms and services:
Slack: Our main communication platform
Notion: Code Documentation, Task Dashboard, Link Database, SCRUM Acrtifacts (Different types of protocols) and Notes
Zoom: For video calls
WhatsApp: Our informal communication platform
Communication Tech Stack Development AI &amp;amp; Data Analysis Python 3.9: We worked mostly in PyCharm, with many different packages and libraries including: StyleGAN2, numpy, torch, librosa, matplotlib.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
