<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MANIFESTO on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b4-manifesto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MANIFESTO on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b4-manifesto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Concept</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b4-manifesto/concept/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b4-manifesto/concept/</guid>
      <description>Concept The Marc Sinan Company shared the main idea with us: how the inner room of a church should be turned into an interactive area where one has to work together with the others; the event should act as a memorial to the victims of the National Socialist Underground murders.
The concept is the project foundation and was developed in collaboration and coordination with the Marc Sinan Company. An important point here was dividing the whole act into substeps to define the possible states of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b4-manifesto/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b4-manifesto/development/</guid>
      <description>Pipeline The implementation of the technical pipeline is divided into three parts. The Manifesto-Core, the Server and the Frontend. A code snippet from the Node.js Server. The processed data will be taken over by a Kafka-Consumer. The circular surfaces which are submitted by the Frontend are compared with the assigned User-IDs from our Kafka instance. After the comparison a decision which signal will be sent to Ableton Live through Ableton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b4-manifesto/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b4-manifesto/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Jira Jira helped to keep our tasks in order and who is doing what regarding creating our concept or the software. Discord With Discord, we had a constant flow of communication. It offers either text- or voice-channels. Miro Miro helped us to collect and order our ideas concerning the project to sort our thoughts. GitHub We shared our codes with the help of GitHub, it made it possible to work on the project simultaneously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b4-manifesto/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b4-manifesto/video/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
