<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MeshHeadz on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MeshHeadz on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/features/</guid>
      <description>Our MeshHeadz application has, as already indicated, a broad spectrum of features but is nevertheless designed to be simple and clear.
Create Your Own Projects After first opening the app, users are able to create as many individual projects as they please, to save their photographs and 3D-models in an organized way. Create Your Own Projects Take Photos With The Built In Camera In order to create a 3D-model of their head, users must be able to include photos they have taken in their projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/process/</guid>
      <description>Design Thinking Process Ever since our team started working together, we have been integrating the method of Design Thinking - a non-linear, iterative process - to our project work. We went back and forth through its six stages to continuously improve our prototype. Design Thinking Process First Steps With a few ideas in mind we spent time researching to come up with potential technologies that best suit our goal and planned our next steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>These are the programming languages and other software products that our application, web service and 3D-pipeline is built on.
Client After detailed research, we decided to develop an Android™ application using the IDE Android Studio. Our decision to use the programming language Java over Kotlin, was based upon the fact that it is the main language that is taught in our studies.
All data that is generated while using the app is stored directly on the device in folders that were especially created for that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b5-meshheadz/future/</guid>
      <description>Many Ideas, Little Time As it often happens while working on a project, the more time passes, the more ideas come to mind. The same happened to us. In the end, we probably could&amp;rsquo;ve spent many additional months developing our product. Short-term Goals In general we think that with more time to develop, we would have become more experienced and therefore more confident in writing efficient code, what would result in our application being faster and the user experience being better.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
