<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Allmende on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b3-allmende/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Allmende on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b3-allmende/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b3-allmende/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b3-allmende/features/</guid>
      <description>Feature set Profile Since allmende is a social network app, a good looking profile page is a must have. That’s why we created a minimalistic profile page for the user to share information about themself, check which challenges they have accomplished and look at their personal posts. Part of every allmende profile is also one of many status icons, which have to be unlocked through challenges, to see if a user is a Tree-Hugger, a Mushroom-Head or something different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b3-allmende/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b3-allmende/process/</guid>
      <description>Idea The original idea for the allmende app came from David Müller, who was the supervisor for our project. He created the app for his master thesis with the goal to inspire people for nature through social-network-structures and gamification. Development After agreeing on recreating the App with React, we briefly familiarized ourselves with it. We devided us in pairs of two, to recreate the given features with react. It took us a great deal of time to rebuild the app and in the end we had to limitate the new features we wanted to implement in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b3-allmende/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b3-allmende/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Communication Discord Discord was the platform the used the most to communicate about the development of allmende. It was the place where we were in constant exchange not only with the team but also with our supervisor David Müller. We took advantage of many useful tools that discord can offer like the creation of threads to discuss features or the up or down-voting of messages to decide whether a feature should be integrated or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b3-allmende/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b3-allmende/future/</guid>
      <description>So, what&amp;#39;s next? Allmende has a huge potentional for the further grow. As the following step we see a development and writing a Rules of Conduct in order to moderate user-generated content. Moreover, Allmende is now accessible in a Webbrowser, the next step would be to make it available for mobile through the channels like Apple Store. Additional Features Like every development team working with a deadline we had to cut out some features that were planned at the beginning but had to be postponed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
