<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Augmenting a Social Game with a Mobile Companion App on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b2-mobile-companion-app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Augmenting a Social Game with a Mobile Companion App on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b2-mobile-companion-app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b2-mobile-companion-app/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b2-mobile-companion-app/features/</guid>
      <description>Features Since the game no longer relies on physical cards and actually closing your eyes or f.e. laying your head onto your arms, we’re able to elude unnecessary complications. Despite that virtualization, the game is mainly determined by the verbal communication between the players on “game days”. The rule structure can be quite complex depending on the player&amp;rsquo;s experience and the choice of rules and roles, thus slowing down the dynamics of the player group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b2-mobile-companion-app/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b2-mobile-companion-app/process/</guid>
      <description>Process At the beginning of the project, there was a brainstorming phase where we as a group wanted to define which games could be considered for an app. We had ideas like: Scotland Yard as a board game, children&amp;rsquo;s games like hide and seek, Werewolf, Settlers of Catan as a board game with landscape cards and figures, Pen &amp;amp; Paper, a mix-up: an app that includes a set of cards and dice almost like a Swiss knife for party games and some more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b2-mobile-companion-app/techstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b2-mobile-companion-app/techstack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack Discord allowed us to organize our communication efficiently, synchronous and asynchronous and enabled us to work together or present current topics via screen sharing.
Miro enabled a lot of planning and visualizing ideas, brainstorming etc.
Unity is the engine we used to create our app with. It is based on C#. We used Netcode network communication.
We used github to work asynchronous and merge the different versions of the project later on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
