<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cargobike Adventures on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cargobike Adventures on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/features/</guid>
      <description>Customizable UI Having built our own customized theme, the site not only meets all the requirements from the business owner but also make it extremely easy to maintain. Through templates and adding php code to each and every UI element on the site, non-programmer admins log in then use customizer to edit image, text, style, layout, hyperlink, adjust navigation, change site info and so on. This of course prolong the frontend development process, but in the long run, it&amp;rsquo;ll save the start-up resources to modify even something as small as a punctuation, and since UI maintaining becomes as easy as it gets, business owners could easily change content up on the Live site without the users seeing any of the changes before publishing them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/process/</guid>
      <description>In the past few months, our project has gone through various phases, and they could be roughly divided into the following segments:
Kicking off Preparation &amp;amp; Planning Database Structure &amp;amp; Website Blueprint Go Live! Booking System Prototyping Kicking off Fortunately, we decided to meet in person very early on and got to do it before the lock down, we went to the start-up company&amp;ndash;Cargobike Adventurer’s site at MotionLab Berlin, a coworking, or co-building, space for entrepreneurs and aspiring inventors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Throughout the whole project, we’ve used many tools alongside with our stack, and they can be organized into the following categories:
Figma &amp;amp; Miro Working on a real world project that has real users and product owners as stakeholders, preparation and planning are indispensable. We started out by using various templates from Miro, the perfect collaboration tool to conduct Product Vision, use cases, user stories, user personas researches. We then draw out our web page layouts, agreed on the color scheme and design elements that fit our product, and created a few UI drafts on the collaborative UI design tool Figma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b6-cargobike-adventures/future/</guid>
      <description>Future features As this app will keep being developed and improved even after the project course is completed, we do have a few ideas of what could be added to it to make it even truer as the one way stop for anything e-bike tour. Feature 1: Create user account with tour posts &amp;amp; plan assistant Besides the site’s recommended tours, we thought that it’d enrich the site to let users create an account and add favorite routes under their profile, and also create their own route and planning similar to blog posts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
