<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>What happened here on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m3-geolocation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in What happened here on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m3-geolocation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m3-geolocation/_features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m3-geolocation/_features/</guid>
      <description>App Home screen One of the core features of the App is the map where users can see their position and all the available points of interest (POI) are indicated with markers. The markers are shown in different colors acoording to the category of the POI. Categories are used to group POI by similar histories. Clicking on a marker will navigate to the detail view of that POI.
Underneath the Map is a modal with a list of all the available POI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m3-geolocation/_process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m3-geolocation/_process/</guid>
      <description>Idea The initial idea for this project was brought to HTW by the Marc Sinan Company, that is currently working on a project creating different audio walks through Berlin in order to educate about its history of forced labour. The task was to build a mobile app, that would allow users to follow the audio tours and navigate them through the city and a content management system, to maintain the data from their side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m3-geolocation/_tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m3-geolocation/_tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack Overview Tech stack Frontend The frontend of our project consists of a mobile app and an editor. To save resources we decided to keep the used technologies of both of them as similar as possible. This way everyone was able to work at the app and the editor interchangeably.
Vue 3
Vue.js is a frontend framework for developing user interfaces. It uses declarative rendering and reactivity to update the DOM upon JavaScript state changes and has great TypeScript support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m3-geolocation/_future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m3-geolocation/_future/</guid>
      <description>General The next step for our project is to contact more institutions who want to cooperate with us. We mainly want to focus on those who treat cultural, historical and social issues. The concept of the app will flourish when more data is added that users can discover.
Trigger warnings As some of the topics present in this app include sensitive content, we want to add the possibility to flag content with trigger warnings, to make sure that everybody can enjoy this app.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
