<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gefahr erkannt, Gefahr gebannt on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gefahr erkannt, Gefahr gebannt on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/features/</guid>
      <description>Training-Related Task To provide an ingame objective which represents an everyday work task to the trainees, their instructors were included in the development process.
When entering the virtual workshop the players receive the task to craft a dice. This requires interaction with cutting machines like the hand lever or the guillotine shears as well as the bench drill to perforate the metal workpieces. To set the final product together, a glue gun needs to be used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/process/</guid>
      <description>Starting off We started this project without any prior experience in the field of occupational safety training and how such is taught. As the need was brought to us in the context of a larger research project, CoLearnET, we scheduled Zoom meetings with educational partners from AVT and bfw. They invited us to visit their workshops in order to gather enough information about the machines being used as well as the potential injuries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Development Our virtual reality safety training prototype was developed with the Unity (2019.4.12f1) game engine. To make use of already implemented basic VR interactions, the SteamVR (1.2.3) plugin as well as the Virtual Reality Toolkit (3.3.0) were chosen. Furthermore, previous developing experience of some group members made it possible to apply past knowledge while shortening learning time. Hardware The application was developed targeting and using the HTC Vive VR headset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/master/m4-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt/future/</guid>
      <description>Our Future Plans Our team is proud of the progress achieved during this semester. We see it as a good foundation for future development.
Furthermore during our user tests we were able to verify what we already assumed: there is a strong request for VR applications to enrich current safety training lessons. User testing was also especially helpful to gather valuable feedback, which we used to generate even more ideas for improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
