<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Migrate the IMI-Map to MEVN on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m6-migrate-the-imimap-to-mevn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Migrate the IMI-Map to MEVN on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m6-migrate-the-imimap-to-mevn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m6-migrate-the-imimap-to-mevn/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m6-migrate-the-imimap-to-mevn/features/</guid>
      <description>The Old IMI-Map The goal of this project was to rewrite the IMI-Map using a new Tech Stack. So we rewrote the app implementing all the features of the old IMI-Map:
Internship Search
Students can search the internship database of the IMI-Map to get inspiration for their own internship. Internship Postponements
Students can request a postponement of their internship using the IMI-Map. These requests can then be processed and accepted or denied by the internship officer using the IMI-Map as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m6-migrate-the-imimap-to-mevn/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m6-migrate-the-imimap-to-mevn/process/</guid>
      <description>Gathering Information First, the team needed to gather information about the internship administration process and the changes that had been made to it due to the COVID19-Pandemic. To do this we repeated the following three steps:
Talk to previous and current internship officers and the student assistants in the internship administration. Understand and visualize the process. Talk about the visualisations and make adjustments accordingly. What to keep? The next step was to evaluate the current IMI-Map and to decide what to keep and what to toss out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m6-migrate-the-imimap-to-mevn/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m6-migrate-the-imimap-to-mevn/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>MEVN MEVN (MongoDB, Express.js, Vue.js und Node.js) as the tech stack had been decided upon before the project started. The study program is increasingly using more modern JavaScript-based frameworks and the IMI-Map was supposed to become more easily integrable into other courses and student projects. MEVN in Detail MongoDB
a document based database which we used with Mongoose Express.js
a JavaScript web framework - used for programming the API Vue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m6-migrate-the-imimap-to-mevn/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m6-migrate-the-imimap-to-mevn/future/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;#39;s next? With this version of the IMI-Map we have achieved a significant improvement over the previous version. We sincerely hope the long tradition of student projects and theses will continue and further generations of IMIs will continue maintaining and improving the IMI-Map.
And we already have a few ideas:
Future Ideas Review Processes
The idea for a possibility of reviewing internships in the IMI-Map has been around since before our project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
