<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Strollr on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b1-strollr-project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Strollr on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b1-strollr-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b1-strollr-project/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b1-strollr-project/features/</guid>
      <description>Feature set Map and Tracking One of the key features of our App is the possibility to pin-point your location and track every move while you&amp;rsquo;re on a stroll out in the wild. With that information, we are creating a Map with the path and pictures you’ve taken along your adventures outside.
Camera and Photo Editor Next up is our Photo Editor. During your time strolling around, you might want to take pictures of all kinds of plants, trees or animals you encounter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b1-strollr-project/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b1-strollr-project/process/</guid>
      <description>Idea The idea for our app originated out of a conversation with a local gardening project. It is an approach to a rather recent question: How do you make spending time in nature more appealing to children and adolescents who grew up on smartphones and other mobile devices? Our supervisor, Prof. Dr. Lenz approached us with his initial idea for a mobile application which already laid out most of the core features that the final version of Strollr incorporates, like the ability to take photos and visualize walks with a map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b1-strollr-project/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b1-strollr-project/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack Com Miro We used our Miro board primarily for planning our weekly meetings ahead of time and as sort of a blank space for brainstorming and working on our project management assignments. The wide variety of tools and plugins was of great benefit to us.
Trello Trello was used to keep track of our Backlog and document the progression of all our tasks. The kanban style layout and handy functions like requirements and deadlines made it the perfect choice for the job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b1-strollr-project/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b1-strollr-project/future/</guid>
      <description>So, what&amp;#39;s next? We already provided the aforementioned gardening project with access to our application for possible test runs in the near future. If it runs stable and proves to be useful, there is potential for a more regular usage, maybe even in other institutions. However, Strollr would have to be deployed through official channels for a widespread release. This poses a financial issue, at least in the case of Apple&amp;rsquo;s App Store.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
