<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vibro2022 on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vibro2022 on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b1/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b1/features/</guid>
      <description>Keyword Search With the help of the Keyword Search you can use words that describe the objects or scene to find a video. In the Original Vibro you had to separate keywords by using a semicolon and the Keyword Search itself was really small. In our new version we implemented chips that can individually be deleted and auto-suggestions to make it more easy for the user to search for Keywords.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b1/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b1/process/</guid>
      <description>Development Our starting point was an already existing program which we wanted to improve. By both testing the program ourselves to understand and get into Vibro and analyzing the experts view, we evaluated the program to find common errors and see which features are more often used and essential for success. In the next step of our process we derived problems, prioritized them and discussed what we actually want to achieve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b1/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b1/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack Com &amp;amp; Design Discord Discord is a voice and text communication program. We used Discord throughout our project mainly for communication. We held our weekly meetings there and also discussed problems or ideas in the chat.
Notion Notion is a project management program that we used to keep track of our to-do&amp;rsquo;s,deadlines,tests and more.
Adobe Illustrator Illustrator was mainly used to illustrate our graphics, design ideas and statistics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Cases</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b1/use-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b1/use-cases/</guid>
      <description>Vibro2018 Use Case Case: Sam sees a video in which first a lion, then a lake is shown. Step 1 Sam enters “Lion“ into the Keyword Search.
Step 2 He starts looking in the Result Map, but isn‘t satisfied with the results there so he thinks painting the lion would help. Sam goes to the Painting-Tool and starts drawing the lion. After he is done, he notes that the drawing didn‘t help him, so he hits UNDO.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
