<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Haptic Globe: Data at your Fingertips on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m6-haptic-globe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Haptic Globe: Data at your Fingertips on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m6-haptic-globe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m6-haptic-globe/_features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m6-haptic-globe/_features/</guid>
      <description>Extendible Prototype All systems for interaction, object tracking, data retrieval and data visualization are designed in a very open and generic way. This makes it easy to extend those functionalities. You can for example easily add new data sources to be visualized on the globe or change the way in which you interact with the data. The following describes our prototypical implementation with a few select data sources to showcase the features and possibilities of those systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m6-haptic-globe/_process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m6-haptic-globe/_process/</guid>
      <description>Because this project was just as much about looking for a solution for bringing real objects into the virtual space as it was about creating an interesting use case, we spent quite some time in the beginning researching possible solutions, before deciding on the hard- and software we would like to go with. Although we spent a substantial amount of time on evaluating the best approach, we still encountered an unexpected problem in the middle of the project, which forced us to stop working on the interactions and figure out another hardware solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m6-haptic-globe/_tech_stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m6-haptic-globe/_tech_stack/</guid>
      <description>Development Unity
Our engine of choice, where all the little pieces come together
https://unity.com/ Oculus
We used the Oculus Rift S and the Oculus Quest with Oculus Link for a pc connection
https://www.oculus.com/ SteamVR
Allowed us to use different headsets without much hassle
https://www.steamvr.com/de/ UltraLeap
For our handtracking we used the Leap Motion and the Stereo IR 170 https://www.ultraleap.com/ Hardware HTC Vive
One of our members had a Vive We additionally used Vive trackers for our globe controller in the beginning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m6-haptic-globe/_future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m6-haptic-globe/_future/</guid>
      <description>Standalone VR Even though the Oculus Quest theoretically could offer hand tracking and a controller at the same time, they currently do not support this via their framework. This forced us to use the Leap Motion for hand tracking which is furthermore tying us to desktop VR. We hope they will open up this functionality in the future, because it would be more portable as a Quest app. Adding more Right now we only use three API’s and four different visualization types, it would be very easy to add more data sources and other ways to visualize the data on the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
