<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>citizenhero on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b4-citizen-hero/</link>
    <description>Recent content in citizenhero on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b4-citizen-hero/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b4-citizen-hero/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b4-citizen-hero/features/</guid>
      <description>Features We wanted to make our web application simple and easy to use because our target users are diverse and we don&amp;rsquo;t expect everyone to be computer savvy. Our web application has the following features:
Know your reps A simple functionality that allows users to filter their representatives by zip code. The representatives&amp;rsquo; names, pictures, political parties, and biographies are then shown. One may also view a specific representative&amp;rsquo;s voting record in parliament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b4-citizen-hero/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b4-citizen-hero/process/</guid>
      <description>Development Our starting point was an idea by our project supervisor, Mr. Till Leinen, and some wireframe designs he had already created to help us visualize his idea. The next step was to develop and implement a game plan. We began with regular Discord meetings to brainstorm ideas. We devised a rough development plan, and our user story mapping helped us in visualizing our MVP and future potential features for our application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b4-citizen-hero/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b4-citizen-hero/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack Discord Discord was our main communication tool for all of our discussions, questions, and progress updates.
Miro Miro was our online white board. We used it for our user story mapping.
Trello Trello was used as our project management tool. It helped us have a good idea of our responsibilities, backlog and completed tasks.
Lucidapp Lucidapp was used to make our project timeline.
Github Github was used to have a general overview and for us to easily work on the code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
