<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recruiter &amp; Employee Match on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recruiter &amp; Employee Match on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/features/</guid>
      <description>User roles In our application we have two roles: recruiter and job seeker. The recruiter can create job offers and job seekers can fill out their resume. Simple sign up The user fills out a questionnaire where they answer questions about the job or employee they are looking for. A job seeker answers questions about their own skills, expectations and values. A recruiter fills out their expectations on a job seeker and information about what their company offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/process/</guid>
      <description>Research Benchmarking &amp;amp; Market Research Compared thoroughly the existing hiring platforms on the market and found out the common issues that users faced while using these platforms.
Created surveys with Google Forms to research user experience with different hiring platforms.
User Research Surveys Conducted surveys to assess the important aspects of the employment process and to figure out the right questions to ask in order to find the top match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Elasticsearch With Elasticsearch we can retrieve data with customized parameters and it will show us the best results based on our query. EJS EJS is a JavaScript template, which essentially allows us to implement JavaScript into HTML files. Thanks to that we were able to display dynamic content on the pages. MongoDB MongoDB is easy to implement with JS, which made it very attractive to us. Its objects can easily be translated to JSON files as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws20/bachelor/b4-rematch-project/future/</guid>
      <description>Here are the features we would have loved to implement if there was more time, of which many were highly requested in the conducted surveys:
More control over matches More matching criterias and filters for the search: To make sure our algorithm works great for personal values, we decided to postpone the implementation of search criterias such as ‘location’ and ‘salary’. We are eager to add them as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
