<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Berlin for Future on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b5-berlin-for-future/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Berlin for Future on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b5-berlin-for-future/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b5-berlin-for-future/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b5-berlin-for-future/features/</guid>
      <description>The vision Our group was tasked by the Berlin Senate with creating two concepts to encourage climate conscious behaviour in students and young people alike. Consequently, this is not just a programming project we’re embarked on this semester.
Thus, our project does not only consist of features, but also of:
climate situation analysis target group, literature, market and app research survey and focus group interviews idea visualisation concept presentation for the Berlin Senate implementation Target group As specified by the Berlin Senate, we were to target students specifically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b5-berlin-for-future/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b5-berlin-for-future/process/</guid>
      <description>Requirements Our project this semester “Berlin for Future” has been made together with the Senate of Berlin. The Senate has been looking for fresh and interesting ideas for making students more aware about climate change.
At our first meeting with the representative from the Senate we asked her about different aspects of the project (expectations, wishes, topic of interest). We found out about an idea of Klimasparbuch(climate savings book) for Berlin, a sustainable guide for the city, which has already been created for some regions in Germany.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b5-berlin-for-future/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b5-berlin-for-future/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Our tech stack Research Tools Google Drive &amp;amp; Google Docs During this stage of our process we relied heavily on our shared Google Drive folder to organize all of our research documents, work protocols and general collection of information. Visualisation Tools Miro We used Miro at the stage where we had more or less concrete concept ideas and needed a place to organize our ideas into concrete features. We also used Miro for our initial wireframes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b5-berlin-for-future/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b5-berlin-for-future/future/</guid>
      <description>So, what&amp;#39;s next? While we have managed to implement our MVP model for the Community Finder Website, we have left the Quiz App implementation wide open for the Berlin Senate, while providing all the designs and MVP functionality ideas. Next steps for Community Finder Comments Section to give the users an option of contacting any community via the app
Categories for communities to provide an easier way of finding desired content</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
