<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Penny Pincher on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b5-penny-pincher/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Penny Pincher on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b5-penny-pincher/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b5-penny-pincher/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b5-penny-pincher/features/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Screen With our App you will find the best bargains! To not be overwhelmed with all of our bargains, you can choose your favorite starting categories on our Welcome Screen when you open the app for the first time. After that you will be sent to the Live Feed. Live Feed The Live Feed is the main feature of this app. Here you can choose one or more of the eleven main categories you&#39;re interested in and see &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b5-penny-pincher/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b5-penny-pincher/process/</guid>
      <description>Idea The initial idea was to create an app that allows users to find bargains easily and efficiently. No matter if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a last minute Christmas present or just want to browse around. With the help of our supervisors Tino Nitze and Jakob Panten we were able to come up with the top feature of our app: the Live Feed - where you get new bargains live! Once we had our first meeting in the Idealo headquarters, we were able to create our git project and had an unofficial Design Sprint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b5-penny-pincher/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b5-penny-pincher/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack Com Discord Discord was our main way of communicating with each other, asking questions and it served as our remote working space. We used voice channels to split into teams and work on different tasks and text channels to inform each other of new pull requests and general info around the project.
Miro We used Miro as a means of sharing our ideas, prototypes, discussing new tasks and updating our progress on the app, basically a place for us to brainstorm during our meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b5-penny-pincher/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b5-penny-pincher/future/</guid>
      <description>So, what&amp;#39;s next? For now we would like to keep working on this project privately and keep improving it! We have come far but there is still a lot that we would like to do.. Additional Features Social Media Hub There are some new features we would like to add in the future such as adding notifications for limited time offers and being able to choose between main and sub categories in browser.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
