<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Allmende 2 on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m6-allmende-2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Allmende 2 on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m6-allmende-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m6-allmende-2/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m6-allmende-2/features/</guid>
      <description>Minimalistic Social Media Application Share your pictures with other people and tag the location and species for your findings! Other people can like and comment your posts to support vivid discussions on your new discoveries! Main Page Comment other posts profile page Species Detection With advanced Deep Learning Technology you can identify over 4000 Species! Just upload your picture and choose a catagory and within seconds you get possible species with their propabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m6-allmende-2/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m6-allmende-2/process/</guid>
      <description>Development Since our goal was clear from the start, we started development early. We devided into 3 teams (Frontend, Backend, Machine Learning) and continued in our teams for the first weeks.
We all came together every Wednesday to discuss our progress and how to continue. We created a kanban board on github to have an overview over pending tasks and our progress in general. We used our own Discord server for further communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m6-allmende-2/challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m6-allmende-2/challenges/</guid>
      <description>Frontend In the Frontend we had componets like the species selector which is a scrollable list of species. We wanted to create an accessible App with a modern user interface. To make the species selector accessible we used a hidden radio button in the background. We made sure that all our components to be accessible and semantically correct. Making all components accssible took us some time. In addition bringing the authentification to work was a more complex task then we first thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m6-allmende-2/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m6-allmende-2/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Architecture architecture The architecture is seperated into three layers: Machine Learning Mircoservice, Backend and Frontend. The Machine Learning Mircoservice get requests from the Backend with an image that should be classified. Inside the Machine Learning Mircoservie a Flask instance is running to handle requests from the Backend. When a image should be classified the TensorFlow Model uses our trained models to classify the image and sends a response with information about which animal could be classified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m6-allmende-2/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m6-allmende-2/future/</guid>
      <description>Chat Implementation Allmende is a social media platform for nature enthusiast. A missing but a mandatory function for a social media app is the ability to chat with other nature enthusiast. Having this feature enables the user the opportunity to communicate in real-time and to connect with others. Edit User Profil For a social media platform it is very important to create a user profil. It would be good to be able to change the profil image.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
