<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ZeroC DataCapture on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b7-zeroc-datacapture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ZeroC DataCapture on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b7-zeroc-datacapture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b7-zeroc-datacapture/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b7-zeroc-datacapture/features/</guid>
      <description>Secure Login The OAuth 2.0 protocoll allows a secure authentication and authorization of users. That was the original idea of how we were supposed to perform the authentication. Unfortunately, there were some complications with its implementation. Therefore, as a plan B we decided to store the login data locally on mobile devices. Display History All the history of added meter data is available to users at any time due to the AsyncStorage technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b7-zeroc-datacapture/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b7-zeroc-datacapture/process/</guid>
      <description>Initial Phase The idea of the project was to create an app for an already existing product that would allow its users to store meter data such as serial number, readings and date on their mobile devices as well as on the backend.
We worked under supervision of Alexander Haferland and Veronika Babic from the Berlin startup urban energy. Veronika also was our Product Manager, who approved or declined our ideas and suggestions and translated to us the urban energy&amp;rsquo;s vision of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b7-zeroc-datacapture/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b7-zeroc-datacapture/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Mockups &amp;amp; Design Figma To develop the design and mockups we used the web version of Figma, a collaborative online platform for designers. Frontend React Native After a continous discussion we decided to create our app with React Native, since most of us already had some experience either with JavaScript or React. React Native is an open-source cross-platform framework for writing native apps that utilizes React and JavaScript. It allowed us to separate the logic into small and reusable components.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
