<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gefahr erkannt, Gefahr gebannt - Teil II on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m7-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt-teil-2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gefahr erkannt, Gefahr gebannt - Teil II on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m7-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt-teil-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m7-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt-teil-2/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m7-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt-teil-2/features/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;You want 33 percent of what&amp;rsquo;s already there, existing, 33 percent improved, and 33 percent brand-new in terms of mechanics&amp;rdquo; (Dennis Shirk, team producer at Firaxis, 2016)
What&amp;#39;s new? While preparing for the showtime we remembered the quote above from the devs at Firaxis, called Sid Meier&amp;rsquo;s 33/33/33 rule of sequel design. Although we didn&amp;rsquo;t stick to it 100%, we think it provides a great way for us to comprehensively break down which parts of our application changed since our previous version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m7-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt-teil-2/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m7-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt-teil-2/process/</guid>
      <description>Our Agile Development Process Starting off Continuing our project allowed us to both reflect on what we had set out to make, what we had made so far, and what we thought would most effectively enhance our product in this second round of development. So far we had made a scene to work in as well as the tools and injuries that can occur from improper use.
The following two questions kicked off the start of this new project iteration:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m7-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt-teil-2/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m7-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt-teil-2/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Our Tech Stack Used Technologies Regarding this point we mostly stayed true to last semester&amp;rsquo;s solutions.
Development The technological foundation we continued working on is realized with the Unity (2019.4.12f1) game engine, expanded by the SteamVR (1.2.3) and the Virtual Reality Toolkit (3.3.0) plugins. For project setup and code versioning we used the same approved GitLab self-hosted solution as last semester.
In terms of the targeted hardware: there were internal discussions at the beginning of the semester about porting the application to a standalone, inside-out-tracking based platform like the Oculus Quest 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m7-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt-teil-2/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m7-gefahr-erkannt-gefahr-gebannt-teil-2/future/</guid>
      <description>Thoughts The cutting edge we have been working on emcompases a number of exciting areas that offer room for expansion.
Gamification Our product (in its current form) makes use of gamification, which remains a debated topic. As with all serious games, the selection and implementation of gamification elements must be carefully made and tested. If done wrongly, such mechanics can be demotivating and, in our case, even harmful, if too much focus is shifted from the actual lessons of workshop safety to the completion of game goals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
