<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blubble - Book Reading Club Application on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b6-book-reading-club-applikation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blubble - Book Reading Club Application on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b6-book-reading-club-applikation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b6-book-reading-club-applikation/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b6-book-reading-club-applikation/features/</guid>
      <description>Features Create, Discover, and Join Book Clubs Once you register in our app, you can create your own club centered around any book of your choice, be it nonfiction or fiction, which you can look up in OpenLibrary containing a vast collection of books from diverse genres and in various languages. After you have created your club, you become its moderator and can modify it by altering the name or increasing the number of members allowed to join.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b6-book-reading-club-applikation/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b6-book-reading-club-applikation/process/</guid>
      <description>The Process Our work was structured in a variance of Scrum. We met twice a week. On Mondays, we met online and presented the current state of our work to each other. It was also necessary for discussing our ideas and suggestions of functionalities or designs. Thursdays we met with our supervisor in the Diva-E office at Berlin Südkreuz to present our achievements, review the past week, discuss problems and plan the next weekly sprint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b6-book-reading-club-applikation/teckstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/bachelor/b6-book-reading-club-applikation/teckstack/</guid>
      <description>Organisation and Communication To keep in touch and keep our communication up and running we used a multitude of well known platforms.
Zoom for our monday meetings Teams for our hybrid thursday meetings WhatsApp for quick questions and coordination Slack for sharing resources and keeping in touch with Diva-E Trello for keeping track of our backlog and our progress on the tickets we wrote Trello Microsoft Teams Zoom Slack WhatsApp Design Miro</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
