<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Intelligentes Bilanzkreismanagement on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m3-intelligentes-bilanzkreismanagement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Intelligentes Bilanzkreismanagement on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m3-intelligentes-bilanzkreismanagement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m3-intelligentes-bilanzkreismanagement/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m3-intelligentes-bilanzkreismanagement/features/</guid>
      <description>Data Visualization Balancing group selection After the user has registered for the app and logged in successfully, it is possible to choose between different balancing groups in order to only show the data the user needs to evaluate. A dropdown menu in the app&amp;rsquo;s header easily allows switching between different balancing groups.
Dashboard The dashboard is the heart of the App, providing organized shortcuts to all features. Its layout automatically adapts to the user&amp;rsquo;s screen by displaying exactly as many widgets as legible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m3-intelligentes-bilanzkreismanagement/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m3-intelligentes-bilanzkreismanagement/process/</guid>
      <description>General Scrum Our entire project management was based on the Scrum framework. To be as flexible and organized as possible, we structured the project into bi-weekly sprints. Before each sprint we did extensive sprint planning, guessing story points that reflect the complexity of each user story and defining what we want to get done within the sprint. If needed, we ended the sprint with a retrospective. Our process also included technical and functional reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m3-intelligentes-bilanzkreismanagement/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m3-intelligentes-bilanzkreismanagement/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack Amazon AWS During the early stages of our project we agreed that we want to run the application as cost-efficient, scalable and performant as possible. We therefore decided to build the system on a serverless architecture using Amazon AWS Lambda functions. The lambda functions only run when they are called through their individual endpoints and provide the latest prediction data generated by the machine learning model. At the end of each month we only have to pay for the computing powert that way required to run these functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m3-intelligentes-bilanzkreismanagement/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m3-intelligentes-bilanzkreismanagement/future/</guid>
      <description>Where we&amp;#39;re at? During the last few months we were able to create a full design library with custom components that allows future designers to enter the project and quickly start designing new components. This was accomplished by keeping the entire figma document clearly and well structured. We were also able to deliver a high-fidelity prototype dashboard that already covers a full basic user flow within a framework that easily allows future developers to add more functionality without compromising for scalability or performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
