<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BEMpsy Buddy on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BEMpsy Buddy on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s BEM?</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/bem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/bem/</guid>
      <description>🤷‍♂️ What exactly does BEM stand for? BEM stands for Betriebliches Eingliederungsmanagement (company integration management). Since 2004, employers have been required by law to offer BEM to all employees who have been incapacitated for work for more than six weeks within a twelve-month period, regardless of the size of the company. The legal basis for this is the Ninth Book of the Social Code (§ 167 Par. 2 SGB IX).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/features/</guid>
      <description>👮 Authentication with OTP While registration or log in, all users need to verify their account with an OTP (One-Time-Password) through email or phone number. This increases the data security and helps securing personal information. eMail Phonenumber Enter Code 😊 Matching &amp;amp; Filter According to given profile information, a specific matching score will be calculated to find the best suiting buddy. Information like illnesses, occupations or languages are analyzed from the application to offer users most effective consultations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/process/</guid>
      <description>⚙️ Workflow Tasks were divided for the backend and frontend team and documented on a kanban board on GitHub. Every thursday an one hour meeting took place with the product owner and the UX-designer to discuss progress and further tasks. This agile workflow made fast changes requested from the product owner possible. After the weekly meeting, the development team reviewed the meeting discussion again and distributed assignments among the members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/challenges/</guid>
      <description>❓ Understanding Concept and Construct Data Structure Model One important challenge was to understand and design an appropriate data model for all given conditions. The first wireframes were not fully finished, which is the reason some frames needed to be more clarified to continue the implementation. 🗣️ Close Cooperation and Communication Overall communication and close cooperation were significant parts of the project since exchanging information about features or general information about the application was crucial for the development process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description> Architecture Communication Design Frontend Backend Miscellaneous </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m3-bempsy-buddy/future/</guid>
      <description>👥 Support Groups For greater support and help, support groups should be integrated in the application. These groups can help users to connect with a number of like-minded users which will make it easier to deal with complicated topics and share similar experiences. Additionally, users who are not BEM entitled or buddies can join these support groups anytime. 🗺️ Map A map shall help users to find buddies near their locations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
