<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Valit on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m7-valit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Valit on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m7-valit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m7-valit/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m7-valit/process/</guid>
      <description>Requirements Analysis The requirements analysis phase of the project was critical in ensuring the successful delivery of a solution that met the needs of both professors and students. To achieve this goal, a comprehensive approach was taken to gather and evaluate all relevant requirements.
The process started with a brainstorming session where all potential requirements were documented. This information was then reviewed and prioritized, focusing on the most important features for both target groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m7-valit/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m7-valit/features/</guid>
      <description>Dashboard The dashboard overview shows important statistics such as the overall course rating and the number of dial-ins. Recent courses for quick access and also upcoming courses, along with a calendar are provided. Course Overview The course overview displays all courses of the lecturer with related information such as semester, degree, program, etc. The lecturer has the option to create a new course, so the application automatically creates an evaluation on the given dates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m7-valit/challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m7-valit/challenges/</guid>
      <description>Choose Must Have Features As meeting the requirements of both students and lecturers often contracted each other we worked on a feature set that encapsulated a common ground between the two. Therefore we carefully selected a stable base feature set and axed features like a Moodle course list import, as we deemed that to be too confusing. Student Login System Another challenge was getting around the barrier of entry for students to fill out the questionnaires and participate in live feedback as well as evaluations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m7-valit/techstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m7-valit/techstack/</guid>
      <description>Concept &amp;amp; Design Miro Miro supported us from the initial brainstorming, through the concrete requirements analysis and conception phase, to the wireframes. It allowed us to discuss and visualize ideas, as well as record decisions.
Figma We used Figma to create our UI component library, the styleguide and final design of the user interface.
Frontend Vue.js To build the web user interface, we felt that Vue.js was suited for our needs: A progressive JavaScript framework that provides incrementally adaptable architecture with the focus on declarative rendering and component composition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m7-valit/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws22/master/m7-valit/future/</guid>
      <description>Not all features made it into our MVP. Either because of scale, time constraints or importance in contrast to the minimum feature set. Here we want to highlight what we wish to add later and also to show a few of the ideas we deem as a fit for Valit.
Editor For Creating Individual Questionnaires The editor will allow users to easily create custom questionnaires by selecting from a variety of question types, such as multiple-choice, open-ended, and rating scales.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
