<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Could it be more Unreal? on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Could it be more Unreal? on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/_features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/_features/</guid>
      <description>Main Menu, Pause Menu, Help Menu Our playable showcase demo offers a main menu with various options to interact with. The HOST button starts a new session and the user acts as a host. The JOIN button has the function of joining an existing session. The button QUIT closes the application. It is required to log in to Steam, when playing the demo, as the demo is only playable with 2 users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/_process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/_process/</guid>
      <description>First things first Every project has a beginning and an end. Before we started doing anything, we were discussing possible ideas for a project. We had to do something with the new Unreal Engine 5, but the question was, what do we want to do? And how do we want to do it? Who wants to do what? To begin with, we had many questions, and we tried to hold all our ideas in a Miro board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/_tech_stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/_tech_stack/</guid>
      <description>Development Unreal Engine 5
Unreal Engine 5 was our main tool.
We built our project and put all small parts together as one. Steam
We were able to play Could it be more Unreal? with Steam multiplayer using the Advanced Steam Sessions plugin. MetaHuman
MetaHuman is a framework that enables anyone to create highly realistic human characters. Modeling Blender
Blender is a 3D content creation software and was used to create assets for our project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/_future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/_future/</guid>
      <description>Many ideas, too little time Due to very limited time and lack of performance optimization, we weren&amp;rsquo;t able to include all features the Unreal Engine 5 has to offer. However, what we might to take a closer look on in the future and fully implement it into our showcase demo could be the following:
Full utilization of 3D Niagara Fluid Simulation
Deeper insight of MetaHuman Creator Extended use of Nanite Virtualized Geometry System Extension possibilities of Could it be more Unreal?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/_team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/_team/</guid>
      <description>The Team We are a team of 8 people in total. This semester, we decided to develop a playable Unreal Engine 5 showcase demo. Each of us had different prior knowledge of the Unreal Engine at the beginning of the project. In the past 4 months we have done our best to demonstrate the new features of the Unreal Engine 5 in a short playable demo. In the process we also encountered various challenges, be it the hardware-hungry Unreal Engine 5, unstable performance or the lack of sufficient repository space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/_credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m1-could-it-be-more-unreal/_credits/</guid>
      <description>(Demo) Credits Emote Sticker &amp;ldquo;I Dont Know&amp;rdquo;:
Sticker created by Freepik - www.freepik.com
Emote Sticker &amp;ldquo;Pointing&amp;rdquo;:
Sticker created by Smashicons - www.smashicons.com
Emote Sticker &amp;ldquo;Binocular&amp;rdquo;:
Sticker created by Slidicon
Sponza Model:
Sponza Model by Intel Corporation
Tower Model:
Tower Model by Aysu
Wooden Bridge Model:
Wooden Bridge by Sanzid
Car Model 1:
Dirty car by 3D Error 404
Car Model 2:
Old Car - VAZ 2107 by Arkady Gribachev</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
