<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AdyBuddy – Obesity Prevention on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m5-adipositas-prevention/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AdyBuddy – Obesity Prevention on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m5-adipositas-prevention/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m5-adipositas-prevention/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m5-adipositas-prevention/process/</guid>
      <description>Research As the very first step of our research, we read multiple studies and articles on the topic obesity and its reduction or prevention in adults as well as in children in order to understand the physiological, psychologial and environmental factors influencing the success or failure of attempted weight loss reduction or weight gain prevention. We summarised our research results on a Miro Board where we collected all our future ideas from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m5-adipositas-prevention/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m5-adipositas-prevention/features/</guid>
      <description>Initial Analysis After the initial registration, the user is asked about their previous exercise and eating habits. By analyzing this data, we assign users to a level of health awareness according to the &amp;ldquo;Stages of Change&amp;rdquo; model. From the data provided, e.g. the amount of fruit and vegetables eaten daily, and the calculated awareness level, we then calculate a percentage increase in the initial value, which forms the basis for the defined goals in the weekly challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m5-adipositas-prevention/challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m5-adipositas-prevention/challenges/</guid>
      <description>Long conceptual phase For about the first five weeks of our project, we were just doing conceptual work. We had to build an entire app without any precise specifications as to what functions it should perform. Therefore, we did many rounds in the first weeks to develop ideas, develop and discard concepts, and finally work out all the important details: What is the unique selling point of our app? What is our target audience?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m5-adipositas-prevention/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m5-adipositas-prevention/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Concept &amp;amp; Design Figma To create our design drafts and final designs, we used the graphics editor Figma. Miro Miro offers a great opportunity to collect and share ideas with all the team members. Frontend Flutter To build our app, we used Flutter. It is an open-source framework from Google that allows you to build platform independent apps, based on the programming language Dart. Android Studio In order to run an emulator for our app, we used Android Studio which is a development environment from Google.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m5-adipositas-prevention/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m5-adipositas-prevention/future/</guid>
      <description>What more is possible? In our conception phase, we came up with a whole bunch of other ideas that we couldn&amp;rsquo;t implement within the limited number of weeks. Here we list a few of these ideas to illustrate the potential that still lies in the app. More educational content We believe that awareness and education is an important key to a lasting healthier life. Therefore, we have planned to provide more prepared content to users in order to provide more knowledge about nutrition and exercise.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
