<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hereiam on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b5-krisen-und-katastrophenmanagement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hereiam on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b5-krisen-und-katastrophenmanagement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b5-krisen-und-katastrophenmanagement/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b5-krisen-und-katastrophenmanagement/features/</guid>
      <description>Map The map is the heart of heriam and is therefore the main page. Even if the user navigates into one of the drawers the map will be displayed in the background. Markers Keeping track of all the dangers and important locations is one of the main functionalities of hereiam, hence the users are able to mark differnt locations and set various points on the map. To keep the points distinguishable the user can choose individual and contrasting icons from a selection of symbols.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b5-krisen-und-katastrophenmanagement/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b5-krisen-und-katastrophenmanagement/process/</guid>
      <description>Idea The original idea for hereiam came from our supervisors who founded hereiam solutions with the vision to create a world that is better prepared for large-scale incidents and catastrophies. The app&amp;rsquo;s goal is to provide a constantly learning and precautionary solution that allows rescue teams to react quickly and dynamically in case of emergencies while staying on top of things. Our team developed the prototype as a starting point for this ambitious endeavour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b5-krisen-und-katastrophenmanagement/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b5-krisen-und-katastrophenmanagement/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Communication, Organisation Slack We used Slack as our main communication and organisation-tool while working on our project. There we could easily gather information and share links that are relevant for our project. Slack also was a good platform to discuss and quickly inform eachother about current problems and difficulties.
Trello Trello was used to keep track of our Backlog.
GitHub For making it easier for us to work on the same codebase together and handle version control we used GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
