<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>easyContract on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b2-easycontract/</link>
    <description>Recent content in easyContract on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b2-easycontract/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b2-easycontract/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b2-easycontract/features/</guid>
      <description>Contract generator Our main feature is the contract generator, which sets the framework for the contract creation process. This enables StartRight to access a database of contract modules more quickly and to create the suitable contract for each customer.
At first the legal form for a new contract should be selected. After that the user can see text blocks, matching the selected legal form. These text blocks can then be inserted into a ready-made text field using drag &amp;amp; drop function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b2-easycontract/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b2-easycontract/process/</guid>
      <description>Brainstorming Idea StartRight wanted an application that would allow them to create contracts faster. After our first conversation and the resulting wishes, we worked out a concept together on how we could simplify the work processes of the student organization. We decided to develop not only the contract generator, but a whole application with additional features. Concept Before planning the concept, we researched existing tools that were similar to our idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b2-easycontract/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b2-easycontract/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>project tech stack Gitlab We used GitLab as our Git hosting platform to have an overview of our code. The idea of ​​Git is simple, using it is difficult. Many of us were able to learn by using Git for the first time in such a large project. After understanding this tool, it followed the actual use in daily practice. Node.js With an open source server environment Node.js we have provided the basis for our platform, as it provides a script structure for websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b2-easycontract/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b2-easycontract/future/</guid>
      <description>So, what&amp;#39;s next? With the first version of easyContract, the work of StartRight will hopefully become easier very soon, but the already existing functions can be further optimized and adapted. Additional Features Completing role assignment through which access rights for the website are controlled. The linking of the calendar and the project overview is a useful extension for assigning notes to an appointment directly to a project. The optimization of the contract generator with regard to the dependencies of the text modules on each other is another big step to help StartRight.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
