<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Complex Space Adventure on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b3-e-learning-komplexer-zahlen/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Complex Space Adventure on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b3-e-learning-komplexer-zahlen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b3-e-learning-komplexer-zahlen/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b3-e-learning-komplexer-zahlen/features/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Who doesn&amp;rsquo;t enjoy a round of &amp;ldquo;Battleship&amp;rdquo;? Inspired by this classic game, we came up with the idea of &amp;ldquo;shooting&amp;rdquo; asteroids and alien spaceships. The coordinate system on which &amp;ldquo;Battleship&amp;rdquo; is also played offers the perfect opportunity to work with complex numbers and make an entertaining but also educational game out of it. Since mathematics and guessing coordinates, even if done strategically, don&amp;rsquo;t really go together, we made some modifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b3-e-learning-komplexer-zahlen/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b3-e-learning-komplexer-zahlen/process/</guid>
      <description>Monitor Spaceship base Space Alien alias Boozeee All together Idea All of us have goals and we do a lot to get closer to them each day. We all also know that it can sometimes be challenging that there are obstacles put in our way. According to our expert, complex numbers are often exactly that challenge for many electrical engineering students during their studies. Most of them have no prior knowledge from school or other areas in this topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b3-e-learning-komplexer-zahlen/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b3-e-learning-komplexer-zahlen/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Communication &amp;amp; Design WhatsApp/Discord For our daily communication we used Discord and WhatsApp. With these apps, we could check in with everyone, ask how things were going, or ask for help. Using Discord, we could also hold a spontaneous meeting if something else needed to be discussed.
Jira We used Jira to create tickets and a backlog to keep track of our project. It helped us define and implement weekly and holistic goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b3-e-learning-komplexer-zahlen/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/bachelor/b3-e-learning-komplexer-zahlen/future/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s hard to make predictions - especially about the future.&amp;rdquo; —Robert Storm Petersen
Further Implementations As Robert Storm Peterson said, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to make predictions, but we&amp;rsquo;re going to try. What we do know is that there are still quite a few game ideas that we can work on in regards of Complex Zahlen. Since we only had one semester to develop the game, we focused on the parts that were most in demand and put the others on hold - at least for now.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
