<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Visual Agenda on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/bachelor/b4-visualagenda/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Visual Agenda on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/bachelor/b4-visualagenda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/bachelor/b4-visualagenda/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/bachelor/b4-visualagenda/features/</guid>
      <description>Features Smart Agenda Planning Say goodbye to haphazard meeting preparations! Our app lets you effortlessly create well-structured agendas within fixed timeframes. Organize topics, set time limits, and ensure your meetings stay on track for maximum productivity.
Timekeeping Made Easy Never overrun your meetings again! With our intuitive timekeeping feature, you&amp;rsquo;ll receive real-time alerts as you approach each agenda item&amp;rsquo;s time limit. Keep everyone focused and make every minute count.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/bachelor/b4-visualagenda/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/bachelor/b4-visualagenda/process/</guid>
      <description>Process Our journey began with a crucial kickoff meeting, where we discussed the project&amp;rsquo;s milestones and set the schedules for their completion. During this meeting, the team collaborated to find suitable meeting days and times that would accommodate everyone&amp;rsquo;s busy schedules. In our subsequent meetings, we focused on comprehensive progress updates. We discussed the tasks we had been diligently working on and candidly addressed any challenges we encountered along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/bachelor/b4-visualagenda/techstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss23/bachelor/b4-visualagenda/techstack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack Communication
For the purpose of communicating with each other we used
Zoom Teams and WhatsApp. Creative Parts
Drafting our ideas and creating anything related to the design we used
Figma Penpot Frontend
Our Frontend was made with
Ionic React Capacitor Backend
Our backend was crafted using
Node.js Socket.io Future Looking ahead, we envision several exciting ideas to enhance Visual Agenda, maximizing its potential and revolutionizing the meeting experience:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
