<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LCvd on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m4-lcvd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LCvd on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m4-lcvd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m4-lcvd/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m4-lcvd/features/</guid>
      <description>Symptom Tracker With LCvd&amp;rsquo;s symptom tracking feature, people who have recovered from COVID-19 can note down their condition on a daily basis. Because there are many possible symptoms, users can select which symptoms to track and update their choice if needed.
New records can be added either in the calendar or graph view, using the plus-button. Records can be edited afterwards using the pen-button.
In the tracker view, users can estimate how strong a symbol is, from a scale from 0 (no symptom) to 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m4-lcvd/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m4-lcvd/process/</guid>
      <description>Design Research With medical apps it is especially important that they are based on scientific research. We started by researching about Long Covid: How is the illness defined? How is it diagnosed? Which are possible symptoms, which are most common and how are they treated? How frequent is Long Covid? What could be the cause of Long Covid? What do Long Covid patients wish for?
Some of our sources are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack and Tool Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m4-lcvd/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m4-lcvd/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack NativeScript-Vue NativeScript is an open-souce framework to access native APIs in JavaScript. With the help of Android Studio and XCode it allows for building truly native applications with a JavaScript frontend framework, in this case Vue.js. During the development emulators have been used to preview the app.
TypeScript TypeScript adds static typing to JavaScript and therefore makes it easier to understand and debug the code. It also transpiles to JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m4-lcvd/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m4-lcvd/future/</guid>
      <description>Beyond the MVP To make patients of Long Covid feel even less alone, our app should also provide
a possibility for them to connect with others in the same situation to exchange experiences a way to document experiences in their own words, like a blog, that they can share with others who are not affected Inputting a vaccination certificate or PCR test result via QR code directly into the app could help to avoid errors and make the app even easier to use.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
