<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graphlands on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b3-dollar-game/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Graphlands on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b3-dollar-game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b3-dollar-game/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b3-dollar-game/features/</guid>
      <description>Levels With currently 30 levels and three difficulties we have a wide range for beginner to professional riddle gamer. All levels have been created and analysed by our team, to support different skills from coordination on the screen to simple mathematics and calculations. Our main menu leads the player to the level screen, which allows the player to choose between easy, normal and difficult graphs. Revisitors are able to see their finished levels in the level selection screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b3-dollar-game/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b3-dollar-game/process/</guid>
      <description>Research Many questions were thrown into the pot upon our first meeting as a group. Since our game is based on graph theory, we needed to decide how we want to design it, what its general goals are and what programming languages and frameworks we want to use. Research and brainstorming was the order of the day. We dedicated our first weeks fully on the first, but very important decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b3-dollar-game/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b3-dollar-game/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Our tech stack Phaser 3 &amp;amp; JavaScript Early on we knew we needed a framework. With JavaScript as a familiar language to most, we decided to aim our search and found Phaser, an open source HTML5 game framework. None of us knew this framework, but we were able to learn as we went. For some time we were not sure if the need for the framework was there, but in the long run it certainly was a good decision to stick with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b3-dollar-game/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/bachelor/b3-dollar-game/future/</guid>
      <description>So, what&amp;#39;s next? We still have many plans! Our game currently allows the player to start with any level and any difficulty he likes. We want to encourage a total play through and will implement unlockable levels in the future. Who knows, maybe you’ll be able to unlock some easter eggs too? More Features Additionally, we are already able to reset singular levels, but what if you want to show it to a friend?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
