<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FixIT! Communication is everything on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m2_4-fixit-communication-is-everything/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FixIT! Communication is everything on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m2_4-fixit-communication-is-everything/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m2_4-fixit-communication-is-everything/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m2_4-fixit-communication-is-everything/features/</guid>
      <description>Extendable first version Throughout the semester we were able to design and develop a first version of our game. Due to the limited time we had to set aside many ideas and compromise on several aspects of the final game design. Keeping that in mind, we made sure to design all aspects of our game intuitively so that the software remains easily extensible. Additionally, we created a documentation of all the tools, assets and further preparations that are needed to get this project up and running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m2_4-fixit-communication-is-everything/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m2_4-fixit-communication-is-everything/process/</guid>
      <description>Organization Our project development was accompanied by weekly meetings with our supervisors on Wednesdays, group meetings on Sundays, and subgroup meetings depending on the individual tasks for that week.
We used Notion as our main project management tool, Google Drive to visualize our progress in weekly presentations, and Discord and WhatsApp for internal communication. Formulating the requirements of the project and determining the research focus defined the first phase of our project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m2_4-fixit-communication-is-everything/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss22/master/m2_4-fixit-communication-is-everything/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Tech Stack Communication &amp;amp; Design Notion We used Notion as our main project management tool. With Notion we were able to create detailed ToDos lists, summarize our brainstorm ideas in organized pages and document our development process.
Google Services With Google Drive we visualized our progress in weekly presentations. We also used the file hosting service as a cloud for all other materials that we stored and shared with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
