<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Find-IT on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m3-find-it/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Find-IT on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m3-find-it/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m3-find-it/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m3-find-it/features/</guid>
      <description>The artificial intelligence engine Our goal is to develop an expert system capable of guessing professions by asking the user a series of questions. This concept is inspired by the Akinator application. By traversing a dynamic tree the software automatically selects a series of questions and it also calculates the score of the user and determines his job, that will allow the artificial intelligence engine to guess as quickly as possible the most suitable professions for the user and determines the technical skills that the user has or not depending on the answers to the questions and gives an assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m3-find-it/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m3-find-it/process/</guid>
      <description>Preparation Steps in the preparation phase This is the first IMI Showtime for some of our group members. In general, we knew what was ahead of us to reach our newly shared goals. After kicking off the project and getting to know each member&amp;rsquo;s strengths and preferences in the scope of the project, as well as our supervisor&amp;rsquo;s visions, we excitingly head on moved to the brainstorm and research phase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m3-find-it/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m3-find-it/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Our tech stack Tech Stack Django/Python When choosing the backend, we had decided to use Python in conjunction with Django. We had the choice to use NodeJS instead, but the final choice was Python in combination with Django. Django offers on the one hand the possibility to set up a SQLIte DB without downloading additional dependencies and on the other hand a fully integrated user-role management system. Furthermore, Django is an excellent tool to implement prototypical approaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m3-find-it/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ss21/master/m3-find-it/future/</guid>
      <description>So, what&amp;#39;s next? The focal point of our project was to create a helpful tool for young students or anyone who wants to reorient themselves in the IT-field. In order to achieve this, the test with the questions and their algorithm was the most important part. Our main forces were being used to ensure that the questions were easy to answer and had psychological value.
Going forward, the next steps would be to expand the database and create more jobs and relevant questions for them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
