<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spiel mich und ich sage Dir wer Du bist! on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b6-spiel-mich-und-ich-sage-dir-wer-du-bist/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spiel mich und ich sage Dir wer Du bist! on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b6-spiel-mich-und-ich-sage-dir-wer-du-bist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b6-spiel-mich-und-ich-sage-dir-wer-du-bist/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b6-spiel-mich-und-ich-sage-dir-wer-du-bist/features/</guid>
      <description>The Game After a shipwreck you find yourself stranded on a small tropical island. Luckily, the island isn&amp;rsquo;t entirely deserted as you find a local inhabitant willing to help you. They would like to bring you to the main island, as there is a ship which might bring you home. But without any money, paying for the fare won&amp;rsquo;t be possible. Luckily though, the Captain offered you a free ride in return for some help around the island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b6-spiel-mich-und-ich-sage-dir-wer-du-bist/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b6-spiel-mich-und-ich-sage-dir-wer-du-bist/process/</guid>
      <description>Idea A personality test has been a popular way of evaluating different characters for a very long time. Whether it’s in a professional business setting, for an academic study, or just for casual private uses. But usually, these tests are just long lists of abstract questions you have to answer with a scale of agree to disagree.
So that brings the question: what if there was another way we could determine a person’s personality other than using questionnaires?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b6-spiel-mich-und-ich-sage-dir-wer-du-bist/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b6-spiel-mich-und-ich-sage-dir-wer-du-bist/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Communication, Organisation Discord Our main communication tool was Discord, since it not only offers different text channels for each department, it also contains voice channels in which we could hold our weekly meeting. Like that we could easily share information, ask quick questions or clarify issues, all while keeping a clear overview.
Trello We used Trello to get an overview for the tasks, which needed to be dealt with. Trello was a good choice because we could label the tasks with how important they are, in which department they fall into.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b6-spiel-mich-und-ich-sage-dir-wer-du-bist/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b6-spiel-mich-und-ich-sage-dir-wer-du-bist/future/</guid>
      <description>So, what&amp;#39;s next? Creating a whole game in such a short time span was no easy task. Basing that game on psychological research even less so. We are very excited to publish a fleshed out game, even if we had to cut some of the planned features short.
There are many ideas we could still expand on. But whether some of us might return to this game, or if we&amp;rsquo;ll all start new projects utilising the experience we gathered during this one, remains to be seen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
