<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Better Spotify on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/</link>
    <description>Recent content in A Better Spotify on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/process/</guid>
      <description>Research Since Spotify – with a whole team of experts behind it – is one of the global players in audio streaming, the question was how the team of seven students could improve the product in a short time. In the beginning, research had to be carried out in various directions in order to be able to identify possible optimisations and restructurings.
Basic questions like the target group and main focus points of our project had to be answered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/features/</guid>
      <description>The Startpage Our unique selling point is our improved Startpage.
Customize the Startpage Better Spotify changes that by replacing the Startpage with a widget system based on a grid layout. The widgets can be chosen by the user to give them the possibility of making the choice whether or not they want certain parts to be displayed.
Additionally, the widgets are moveable via drag-and-drop which makes it even easier for the user to customize the Homepage to their own needs and wishes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/challenges/</guid>
      <description>Queue Even though at the beginning of the project, the team was certain that working on the queue would be a big step and a big part of Better Spotify, in the end, the queue was dropped.
This had more than just one reason that all worked together to get to the final decision of dropping the tickets entirely even though the biggest one would have already been enough for the team to decide on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Typescript Typescript Typescript is the programming language that was used in both front- and backend. It compiles to Javascript but provides more features like type-safety. This avoids runtime errors and improves development flow with suggestions in the IDE. Backend NodeJS A Javascript runtime used in the backend ExpressJS A backend web application framework for NodeJS Frontend React React is a widely used frontend JavaScript library that provides user interfaces and was used to work on the visuals and UI components Sass Sass is a scripting language that is preprocessed and then converted into normal CSS to be read by the browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/master/m2-a-better-spotify/future/</guid>
      <description>Overview As Better Spotify is an application that was created solely to provide an improved version of an already existing streaming platform, the possible extensions to it are truly endless. To give a short idea of what had been planned by the team but discarded due to the time restrictions, only a selected few of the 30+ ideas in the backlog will be explained. Comment function One improvement that the focus group had talked about and one of our team members had found during research was the possibility of leaving a comment on a song.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
