<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Studyplan on IMI Showtime</title>
    <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b4-bessere-wahlpflichtkursbelegung/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Studyplan on IMI Showtime</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b4-bessere-wahlpflichtkursbelegung/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b4-bessere-wahlpflichtkursbelegung/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b4-bessere-wahlpflichtkursbelegung/features/</guid>
      <description>Elective course registration Ranking System (by HTW) The ranking system provided by the HTW is still the most important set of rules that we had to follow and we could not change it for the course distribution. Although the ranking system might sound fair at first, the students from the higher ranks have the opportunity to receive courses without restriction. This could lead to people getting courses they only wanted as an insurance for the case that they do not get a different course, while other people do not get to attend it, even though it might have been the course they wanted the most.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b4-bessere-wahlpflichtkursbelegung/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b4-bessere-wahlpflichtkursbelegung/process/</guid>
      <description>Brainstorming feature ideas &amp;amp; prioritizing During the beginning of the project, we still had the chance to meet in person, which was really helpful when collecting all of our ideas. Our supervisors initial idea was to make the elective course registration for the IMI students easier, which can be accomplished in a variety of ways. This led us to a long period of time where we thought about different approaches and how realistic it is for us to achieve these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Stack</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b4-bessere-wahlpflichtkursbelegung/tech-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b4-bessere-wahlpflichtkursbelegung/tech-stack/</guid>
      <description>Developing Tools For the developing process, we used the &amp;ldquo;MEVN&amp;rdquo; stack, which consists of widely used and good documented tools to build a web application with HTML, CSS and Javascript. The tool that we worked the most with from this stack was Vue.js, since it is easy to learn and had the advantage of being reactive.
source: https://www.arkasoftwares.com/images/inner-pages/mevn-stack-functions.png MongoDB
document based database Express.js
JavaScript web framework that extends Node.js Vue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future</title>
      <link>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b4-bessere-wahlpflichtkursbelegung/future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://martamurawska.github.io/showtime-website/ws21/bachelor/b4-bessere-wahlpflichtkursbelegung/future/</guid>
      <description>Extensions Our task was to make the elective course registration for IMI bachelor students easier. However, our final product can easily be extended, which will probably be done in a bachelor thesis.
All HTW students Since the studyplan can only help IMI bachelor students with their elective course registration and organization so far, the next step would be to make it usable for master students and someday all the other students as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
